A Guide to the Papers of the Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1927-1953
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Correspondance and Miscellaneous Records (Box 54-145)
  - Edwin S. Friendly--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Frank H. Fuller [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Grigore Gafencu 1952 (Box 132)
  - Dr. Kenneth J. Galbraith--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Lewis Galentiere 1952 (Box 132)
  - John Gange [1953] (Box 132)
  - Leonard Ganse [1953] (Box 132)
  - Mrs. K. C. Garrique [1953] (Box 132)
  - Hon. J. Vaughan Gary 1951 (Box 132)
  - Dr. Wilson Gee--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Dr. Walter Gellhorn [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - General--University of Virginia 1950, 2 folders (Box 132)
  - General Education Board [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Frank Gibney [1953] (Box 132)
  - Gerhard Glaser [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Dr. Meta Glass [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Robert K. Gooch 1951 (Box 132)
  - 1951 [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Hon. Albert S. Goss--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Governor [1950-1951] (Box 132)
  - Governors Delegates--Acceptances 1952 (Box 132)
  - Letters to Governors East of the Mississippi 1952 (Box 132)
  - Governors and Embassies 1952 (Box 132)
  - John Temple Graves 1951-1952 (Box 133)
  - Hon. Gordon Gray--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Dennis Greenhill 1951 (Box 133)
  - Bernard Greensfelder 1951 (Box 133)
  - Alfred Griswold 1951 (Box 133)
  - Bertram M. Gross--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Ernest A. Gross, U.S. Ambassador 1951 (Box 133)
  - Feliks Gross 1952 (Box 133)
  - Gen. Alfred M. Gruenther--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 133)
  - Prof. James Hart--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Hale--Introductions, Evening Speakers 1953 (Box 133)
  - 1953, 2 folders (Box 133)
  - Dr. Oron J. Hale 1951 (Box 133)
  - P. W. Han [1953] (Box 133)
  - H. F. Harding 1951 (Box 133)
  - Averell Harriman 1952 (Box 133)
  - Kenneth Harris 1951 (Box 133)
  - Joseph C. Harsch 1951 (Box 133)
  - Dr. James Hart 1952 (Box 133)
  - M. Salah Hassan 1952 (Box 133)
  - Dr. Claude E. Hawley--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Harry Hazlitt 1952 (Box 133)
  - Horace E. Henderson [1953] (Box 133)
  - Dr. H. J. Heneman--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Robert E. Henley 1951 (Box 133)
  - Pendleton Herring, Esq. 1952 (Box 133)
  - William C. Hetherington [1953] (Box 133)
  - Ida Himes 1951 (Box 133)
  - Paul G. Hoffman 1951-1952 (Box 133)
  - Prof. Arthur Holcombe 1952 (Box 133)
  - Thomas Holland 1951 (Box 133)
  - Mrs. Peggy Homan [1953] (Box 133)
  - Calvin B. Hoover [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Harold B. Hoskins 1952 (Box 133)
  - Hostess 1952 (Box 133)
  - Hotel Reservations [1950-1951] (Box 133)
  - Housing [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 133)
  - Housing Dormitories 1953 (Box 133)
  - Housing Facilities for Institute Visitors 1952 (Box 133)
  - Coulter Huyler [1953] (Box 133)
  - Information--Bound Copies of Proceedings 1953 (Box 133)
  - Inquiries 1952 (Box 133)
  - Institute and Forum Programs 1951 (Box 133)
  - Institute, Comments on the 1952 (Box 133)
  - Institute Letters--Written by President Darden 1952 (Box 133)
  - Institute of International Education 1951 (Box 133)
  - Institute Speeches--Miscellaneous 1952 (Box 133)
  - Introduction of Speakers [1950-1951] (Box 134)
  - Introduction of Speakers and Opening Remarks 1951 (Box 134)
  - Invitation List 1951 (Box 134)
  - Invitation Lists--Receptions, etc. [1950-1951] (Box 134)
  - Invitations--Formal, Samples [1950-1951] 1953 (Box 134)
  - Invitations to Participants 1953 (Box 134)
  - Invitations to Participants--Speakers Declined 1953, 2 folders (Box 134)
  - Invoices [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 134)
  - Invoices, Copies of 1953 (Box 134)
  - Invoices, Rendered 1953-1954 (Box 134)
  - Hon. Robert Jackson 1952 (Box 134)
  - Hon. Philip C. Jessup--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 134)
  - Eric Johnson 1952 (Box 134)
  - Dr. Joseph E. Johnson 1952 (Box 134)
  - Clem D. Johnston [1950-1951] (Box 134)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce--State [1950-1951] (Box 134)
  - Joseph D. Keenan 1951 (Box 135)
  - Hon. Estes Kefauver 1951 (Box 135)
  - Sidney S. Kellam 1952 (Box 135)
  - Rev. William J. Kelley 1951 (Box 135)
  - Dr. George F. Kennan--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - Howard Kershner 1951 (Box 135)
  - Prof. Stephan D. Kertesz 1952 (Box 135)
  - V. O. Key 1952 (Box 135)
  - Leon Keyserling--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - Vice-Admiral Alan Kirk 1952 (Box 135)
  - Dr. Samuel K. C. Kopper 1951 (Box 135)
  - Arthur Krock 1952 (Box 135)
  - Harry Krould [1953] (Box 135)
  - Ferdinand Kuhn--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - Wm. S. B. Lacy--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - James M. Landis 1952 (Box 135)
  - League of Women Voters [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - Dr. Humphrey Lee--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - Mrs. John G. Lee 1952-1953, 2 folders (Box 135)
  - Legations--Washington, D.C. 1952 (Box 135)
  - Shao Chuan Leng 1951, 1953, 2 folders (Box 135)
  - Max Lerner--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 135)
  - Letters 1952 (Box 135)
  - Letters--Bound Copies 1952 (Box 135)
  - Letters--Dictated by John Lloyd Newcomb 1953 (Box 135)
  - Letters--1953 Institute 1953 (Box 135)
  - Geoffrey Lewis 1953 (Box 135)
  - Library Orders--Bound Copies 1953 (Box 135)
  - Hon. Trygve Lie--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - Hon. David E. Lilienthal 1952 (Box 135)
  - Dr. Paul Linebarger 1951 (Box 135)
  - Walter Lippmann 1951-1952 (Box 135)
  - List--see also Mailing 1951-1952 (Box 135)
  - List of Donors 1953 (Box 135)
  - List of Participants--1951 Institute 1951 (Box 135)
  - List of Possible Contributors [1950-1951] (Box 135)
  - List of Refusals to Contribute 1951 (Box 135)
  - Lists--Donors 1950-1951 (Box 135)
  - Dr. Edward H. Litchfield 1951 (Box 135)
  - J. A. Livingston 1953 (Box 135)
  - Senator Henry Cabot Lodge--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 135)
  - Joseph A. Loftus 1951 (Box 135)
  - Miss Edna Lonigan 1952 (Box 135)
  - Luce's Press Clipping Bureau 1950-1953 (Box 135)
  - Luce's Press Clippings 1952, 2 folders (Box 136)
  - Norman G. Luker 1953 (Box 136)
  - Gen. Douglas A. MacArthur 1952 (Box 136)
  - J. J. McCloy 1952 (Box 136)
  - Admiral Lynde Dupuy McCormick 1952 (Box 136)
  - Robert L. L. McCormick 1952 (Box 136)
  - Wesley McCune--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 136)
  - Dr. Joseph M. McDaniel--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 136)
  - George C. McGhee 1951 (Box 136)
  - Archibald MacLeish 1952 (Box 136)
  - Gen. G. A. L. MacNaughton [1950-1951] (Box 136)
  - Douglas B. Maggs 1951 (Box 136)
  - Mail--Messenger 1954 (Box 136)
  - Mailing List--Bound Copies 1951 (Box 136)
  - Mailing List--Current 1952 (Box 136)
  - Mailing List--Director's Report 1951 (Box 136)
  - Mailing List 1951 Session 1951 (Box 136)
  - Mailing List--Programs 1953 (Box 136)
  - Mailing Lists [1950-1951] (Box 136)
  - Mailing--Second Class Information 1951 (Box 136)
  - Hon. Charles H. Malik 1951 (Box 136)
  - Dr. Carl Marcy [1953] (Box 137)
  - Charles F. Marsh--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Gen. George C. Marshall 1952 (Box 137)
  - Edwin M. Martin 1951 (Box 137)
  - Georges Henri Martin [1953] (Box 137)
  - Prof. Edward S. Mason [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Maj. John A. Mathews--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - John M. Maury Jr. [1953] (Box 137)
  - William S. Meacham--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Gardiner C. Means--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Meetings--Minutes [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Membership Lists--Paid [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - James H. Michael, Jr. 1952-1953 (Box 137)
  - Drew Middleton 1951 (Box 137)
  - Raymond F. Mikesell--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Stanislaw Mikolajczvk 1952 (Box 137)
  - Alvah Miller 1952 (Box 137)
  - Francis Pickens Miller--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Mrs. Helen Hill Miller--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - Spencer Miller--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 137)
  - George Fort Milton 1952 (Box 137)
  - Miscellaneous "A--O" [1950-1953], 16 folders (Box 137)
  - Miscellaneous "P--Z" [1950-1953], 8 folders (Box 138)
  - Hon. W. Morgenstierne--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 138)
  - Dr. Hans Morgenthau 1952 (Box 138)
  - Admiral Ben Morreell 1952 (Box 138)
  - Mrs. Edward Morris 1951 (Box 138)
  - Robert Morris [1953] (Box 138)
  - Harold G. Moulton 1952 (Box 138)
  - Lewis Mumford 1951 (Box 138)
  - Philip Murray 1952 (Box 138)
  - Edward R. Murrow--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 138)
  - New York Times 1951 (Box 138)
  - New York Times Correspondents 1951 (Box 138)
  - John Lloyd Newcomb's Letters 1952 (Box 138)
  - President Walter S. Newman--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 138)
  - News Letter 1951-1953 (Box 138)
  - Newspaper Clippings [1950] (Box 138)
  - Dr. Reinhold Niebuhr--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 138)
  - Dr. Justin Wroe Nixon--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 138)
  - Dr. O. F. Nolde--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 138)
  - Fritz Nolting--Accepted [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 138)
  - Dr. Edwin G. Nourse 1952 (Box 138)
  - Oak Ridge Nuclear Studies--Atomic Energy [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Operating Expenses 1951 (Box 139)
  - Operating Statement 1950 (Box 139)
  - Dr. J. Robert Oppenheimer--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Orders--Office Supplies 1952 (Box 139)
  - Organizations--Written to 1952 (Box 139)
  - Dr. Stefan Osusky 1951-1952 (Box 139)
  - "Outlook for the Free World"--see Clippings and Program 1953 (Box 139)
  - Pace's Taxi Service 1953 (Box 139)
  - Ralph Paine, Esq. 1952 (Box 139)
  - Madam Vija Lakshmi Pandit 1951 (Box 139)
  - Panel Letters to be Segregated 1952 (Box 139)
  - Panel Members--Declinations 1952 (Box 139)
  - Panel Participants 1950 (Box 139)
  - Participants--List of 1952 (Box 139)
  - Miss Margaret Parton 1953 (Box 139)
  - Pay-Roll--Hourly and Weekly Employees 1953 (Box 139)
  - Pay-Rolls and Information--Temporary Employees 1953 (Box 139)
  - Dr. Nathaniel Peffer--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Personnel Department 1952-1953 (Box 139)
  - Personnel--Office 1950 (Box 139)
  - Persons asking about single copy speeches 1952 (Box 139)
  - List of Persons to Contact 1952 (Box 139)
  - Lists of Persons Written To 1952 (Box 139)
  - Cabell Phillips--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Joseph Phillips 1952 (Box 139)
  - Photographs 1950 (Box 139)
  - Dr. Clarence E. Pickett--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Dr. Raymond B. Pinchbeck--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Pledges Outside the University 1953 (Box 139)
  - John Garland Pollard--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Ivo Porter 1953 (Box 139)
  - Possible Contributors 1952 (Box 139)
  - Possible Speakers [1950-1951] (Box 139)
  - Dr. Stefan T. Possony 1953 (Box 139)
  - Philip Potter 1951 (Box 139)
  - Preliminary Announcement 1950-1951 (Box 139)
  - Preliminary Announcement--Letter to Newspapers 1952 (Box 139)
  - Preliminary Program--Copy 1952 (Box 139)
  - Colonel William M. Preston 1951 (Box 139)
  - Proceedings of Institute 1953 (Box 139)
  - Professors who Participated 1950 (Box 139)
  - Program [1950] (Box 139)
  - Program Materials 1953-1954 (Box 140)
  - Program in Revision 1950, 2 folders (Box 140)
  - Public Affairs--Clippings 1953-1954 (Box 140)
  - Publicity 1950-1953 (Box 140)
  - Publicity--Alumni News 1951 (Box 140)
  - Purchasing Department 1950 (Box 140)
  - Obaidur Rahman 1952 (Box 140)
  - Clarence Randall 1952 (Box 140)
  - Receipts from Sale of Copies of 1950 Bound Proceedings 1951 (Box 140)
  - Reception [1950-1952] (Box 140)
  - Recommendations--Clerical Jobs, Institute 1950 (Box 140)
  - Philip D. Reed [1950-1951] (Box 140)
  - Registration Fee Paid in Advance 1953 (Box 140)
  - Registration--Information Concerning 1953 (Box 140)
  - Registration--Letters and Checks 1953 (Box 140)
  - William Reitzel [1953] (Box 140)
  - Replies to Darden's Letter Asking for Contributions [1950-1951] (Box 140)
  - Report and Budget 1950 (Box 140)
  - Report--1950 Session, Lists of to Whom Sent 1950 (Box 140)
  - Report--1951 Session 1951 (Box 140)
  - Report--17th Session 1950 (Box 140)
  - Request for 1951 Program 1951 (Box 140)
  - Reservations--Rooms 1950-1953 (Box 141)
  - Reservations--Speakers 1951 (Box 141)
  - Dr. James Reston--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - F. D. G. Ribble--Accepted [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 141)
  - Donald R. Richberg 1952-[1953] (Box 141)
  - Richmond Chamber of Commerce [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Richmond Junior Chamber of Commerce [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch Representative 1951 (Box 141)
  - Dr. Louis N. Ridenour, Jr.--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Leonard Rist [1953] (Box 141)
  - Hon. A. Willis Robertson 1951 (Box 141)
  - Walter S. Robertson--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Stefan H. Robock--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Rockefeller Foundation 1953 (Box 141)
  - Nelson D. Rockefeller 1951 (Box 141)
  - Dr. Louis H. Rohrbaugh--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Charles P. Romulo 1951 (Box 141)
  - Rooming Facilities [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Mrs. Eleanor Roosevelt 1952 (Box 141)
  - Frederick T. Rope 1951 (Box 141)
  - Anna M. Rosenberg 1951 (Box 141)
  - Rotary Clubs [1950-1951] 1953 (Box 141)
  - Rotary Club of Charlottesville [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Rotary International 1951-1952 (Box 141)
  - Richard C. Rowsom 1953 (Box 141)
  - Melville Ruggles [1953] (Box 141)
  - Hon. Dean Rusk--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 141)
  - Senator Richard B. Russell 1952 (Box 141)
  - Hon. Leverett Saltonstall 1951-1952 (Box 141)
  - Paul D. Sanders--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - David Sarnoff 1952 (Box 141)
  - Richard M. Scammon 1952 (Box 141)
  - Dr. Arthur M. Schlessinger, Jr.--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Dr. Emerson Schmidt 1951 (Box 141)
  - Harmut Schulze-Boysen [1953] (Box 141)
  - Charles Schwarz--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Secretarial Help for Institute 1952 (Box 141)
  - Secretarial and Office Help [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Dr. S. R. Shafag 1952 (Box 141)
  - Mabel Shannon 1951 (Box 141)
  - Eleanor Shea 1953 (Box 141)
  - Sidney Sherwood [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Earl Shifflet--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Demitri Shimkin [1953] (Box 141)
  - Boris Shishkin 1952-[1953], 2 folders (Box 141)
  - Dr. George N. Shuster 1953 (Box 141)
  - Baron Silvercruys 1951 (Box 141)
  - Dr. Hans Simons 1951 (Box 141)
  - Frederick G. Singer [1953] (Box 141)
  - Jeanne Singer 1951 (Box 141)
  - Prof. Theodore A. Smedley--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Leroy H. Smith 1951 (Box 141)
  - Hon. Margaret Chase Smith 1952 (Box 141)
  - Dr. T. V. Smith--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 141)
  - Hon. Walter Bedell Smith 1952 (Box 141)
  - Dr. T. R. Snavely--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 141)
  - Solicitation of Contributions 1951-1953 (Box 142)
  - Prof. Carl B. Spaeth 1951 (Box 142)
  - Speakers [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Speakers and Discussion Leaders [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Speeches and Excerpts 1952 (Box 142)
  - Speeches Sold and Bills Sent 1953 (Box 142)
  - Charles Spofford 1952 (Box 142)
  - Elmer Staats 1951 (Box 142)
  - Stamps 1953 (Box 142)
  - State Chamber of Commerce [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - State Department of Education 1950 (Box 142)
  - Statement of Cost--1952 Institute 1952 (Box 142)
  - Statement of Registration Fees--Paid [1950-1952] (Box 142)
  - Statistics [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 142)
  - Statistics--1951 Session 1951 (Box 142)
  - Wm. F. Stauffer--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - William Stead--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Herman W. Steinkraus--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Thomas Stokes 1951 (Box 142)
  - Shepard Stone 1953 (Box 142)
  - Michael Straight [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Student Acceptances 1953 (Box 142)
  - Student Arrival Times [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Student Assistants 1952 (Box 142)
  - Student Attendance [1950-1951] (Box 142)
  - Student Delegates--Accepted 1952 (Box 142)
  - Student Delegates--Invited 1952 (Box 142)
  - Student Housing 1952 (Box 142)
  - Student Representatives 1951, 2 folders (Box 143)
  - Subscribers, 1942--Letters to 1953 (Box 143)
  - Subscribers to the 1952 Proceedings 1952 (Box 143)
  - Dr. Sidney Sufrin 1952 (Box 143)
  - Suggestions [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Suggestions for Improvement [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Suggestions for Speakers and Panel Participants [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Suggestions for Themes [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Summer Quarter 1953 (Box 143)
  - Supplies--Orders 1950-1951 (Box 143)
  - Supplies, Orders for--University Press 1953 (Box 143)
  - Senator Robert Taft--Declined [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 143)
  - Phillips Talbot 1951 (Box 143)
  - Teachers--Invitations [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Telegrams [1950-1951] 1953 (Box 143)
  - Telegrams--Copies of [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Tentative Budget 1952-1953 (Box 143)
  - Tentative Program 1952 (Box 143)
  - George Terbough--Declined [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Dr. Lorin A. Thompson--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Tours--Europe [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Transportation--Balch [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Travel Vouchers [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 143)
  - Travel Vouchers and Communication [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Typewriter Contract with the Purchasing [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Unbound Speeches--Sold [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - University Press [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - University Press--see also Supplies 1952-1953 (Box 143)
  - University of Virginia Professors [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Dr. R. W. Van Wagenen 1951-1952 (Box 143)
  - Prof. Amory Vanderbosch [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Hon. H. J. van Mook [1950-1951] (Box 143)
  - Vesper Service [1950-1951] 1952 (Box 143)
  - Vespers 1953 (Box 144)
  - Virginia Education Association [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Virginia Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1953 (Box 144)
  - William Vogt 1953 (Box 144)
  - Countess Waldeck 1952 (Box 144)
  - Felix Warburg 1952 (Box 144)
  - Hon. James P. Warburg [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Gov. Earl Warren 1951 (Box 144)
  - Lt. Gen. Albert C. Wedemeyer 1952 (Box 144)
  - Dr. Alvin M. Weinberg--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Welfare State--Requests for Information [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Robert West [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Robert West--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - J. Russell Wiggins 1952 (Box 144)
  - Harvie Wilkinson--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Charles Williams [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Hon. Charles E. Wilson 1951-1952 (Box 144)
  - Mrs. Mary R. Wilson [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Ellen Winston--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Lucy Wise--Party at Farmington 1952 (Box 144)
  - Arnold Wolfers, Esq. 1952 (Box 144)
  - Matthew Woll 1952 (Box 144)
  - Dr. Nathan H. Woodruff--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - Dr. Edwin M. Wright 1953 (Box 144)
  - Hon. Hume H. Wrong--Accepted [1950-1951] (Box 144)
  - British Information Service n.d. (Box 144)
  - Requisitions--Supply Room n.d. (Box 144)
  - Speakers at the Institute n.d. (Box 144)
  - Publicity 1925-1935, 6 folders (Box 144)
  - Printed Material
    - Daily Schedules 1928-1938 (Box 144)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material 1927-1951 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1927 September 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1927 October 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1928 July 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1929 August 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1930 August 1 (Box 145)
    - University of Virginia Alumni News 1930 September (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1931 May 15 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1931 April 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1932 June 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1933 June 15 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1934 June 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1935 June 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1936 June 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1937 June 1 (Box 145)
    - Summer Quarter Bulletin 1938 June 1 (Box 145)
    - Program 1939 July 3-15 (Box 145)
    - Program 1940 June 14-24 (Box 145)
    - Program--Preliminary Issue 1941 June-July (Box 145)
    - Program 1941 June-July (Box 145)
- Series IV: Bound Proceedings (Box 145-148)
  - Bound Proceedings--15th Session 1941 June 22-July 4, 1 volume (Box 145)
    RG/2/4/1.892
  - Bound Proceedings--17th Session 1941 June 22-July 4, 2 volumes (Box 146)
  - Bound Proceedings--17th Session 1950 July 9-15 (Box 147)
  - Bound Proceedings--18th Session 1951 July 8-14 (Box 147)
  - Bound Proceedings--19th Session 1952 June 26-July 2 (Box 148)
  - Bound Proceedings--20th Session 1953 July 5-11 (Box 148)
- Series V: Tape Recordings (Reel T411-T416)